A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Special Collections, Signature Letters FA1480
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Signature Letters from Individuals, 1949-1998; 2
  - Hei-Hi - Individuals, 1952-1965 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    Herter, Christian Archibald, Jr. - 1952-1964 (12 letters)
    Hesburgh, Theodore Martin - 1958-1965 (5 letters)
    Hess, Thomas B. - 1960
    Hilsman, Roger - 1962 (2 letters)
    Hightower, John Brantley - 1964
  - Ho-Hug - Individuals, 1951-1967 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    Hoff, Philip H. - 1965-1967 (2 letters)
    Holland, Spessard Lindsey - 1958
    Hoover, John Edgar - 1966
    Hoover, Herbert - 1951-1960 (2 letters)
    Houle, Cyril Orvin - 1958 (3 letters)
    Houseman, John - 1964
    Hoving, Thomas P.F. - 1967
    Hughes, Richard Joseph - 1962 (2 letters)
  - Hum-Hut - Individuals, 1951-1969 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    Humphrey, Hubert Horatio - 1955-1969 (25 letters)
    Humphrey, Hubert Horatio - 1969 (actually Kissinger, Henry)
    Hutchins, Robert Maynard - 1951-1962 (3 letters)
  - I - Individuals, 1951-1973 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    Ickes, Harold L. - 1951
    Irving, Jules - 1958-1973 (20 letters)(1 missing)
    Ismay, General Lord - 1957
    Ives, Irving M. - 1958
  - Ja - Individuals, 1956-1969 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    Jackson, Henry Martin - 1956-1966 (9 letters)
    James, Philip - 1962
    Janov, Arthur - 1958
    Javits, Jacob Koppel - 1961-1969 (22 letters)
    Javits, Marion (Mrs. Jacob Koppel) - 1966 (2 letters)
  - Je-Jo - Individuals, 1951-1967 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    Jenkins, Newell - 1959
    Jenkins, Paul - 1959
    Jessup, Philip C. - 1959
    Johnson, Byron L. - 1959
    Johnson, Lyndon Baines - 1957-1961 (3 folders)
    Johnson, Philip – 1962
    Joio, Norman Dello - 1967
    Jones, Harrison - 1951
  - Ka-Kef - Individuals, 1955-1988 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    Kahn, Louis I. - 1959
    Kampmann, Viggo - 1961
    Katims, Milton - 1961-1964 (2 letters)
    Katzenbach, Nicholas deB. - 1957-1962 (3 letters)
    Kaufmann, Edgar, Jr. - 1962 (2 letters)
    Kazan, Elia - 1959-1965 (2 letters)
    Kazi-Ferrouillet, Kuumba - 1988
    Keating, Kenneth B. - 1960-1965 (2 letters)
    Keeney, Barnaby Conrad - 1967
    Kefauver, Estes - 1955-1961 (2 letters)
  - Kennan - Individual, 1951-1960 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    Kennan, George Frost - 1951-1960 (16 letters)
  - Ken-Kh - Individuals, 1956-1987 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    Kennedy, Edward Moore - 1966-1987 (3 letters)
    Kennedy, Rose - 1956
    Kennedy, Robert Fitzgerald - 1962-1964 (2 letters)
    Kennedy, Robert Francis - 1962-1967 (2 letters)
    Kenyatta, Jomo - 1962
    Kenyatta, Margaret - 1961
    Keppel, Francis - 1963-1964 (2 letters)
    Kerner, Otto - 1966
    Kerr, Clark - 1963
    Khan, M. Ayub 1961
    Kheel, Theodore Woodrow - 1956-1963 (5 letters)
  - Kie-Kip - Individuals, 1955-1966 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    Kiernan, Thomas J. - 1963-1964 (2 letters)
    King, Martin Luther, Jr. - 1965 (2 letters)
    Kinsey, Alfred Charles - 1955-1966 (6 letters)
    Kiplinger, Willard M. - 1962-1965 (6 letters)
  - Kir - Individuals, 1956-1968 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    Kirk, Grayson - 1956-1968 (15 letters)
    Kirstein, Lincoln - 1959-1965 (4 letters)
  - Kissinger - Individual (4 folders), 1951-1970 (Box 6, Folder 57, Box 7, Folder 58-60)
    Kissinger, Henry Alfred - 1951-1970 (85 letters)
  - Kn-Ku - Individuals, 1950-1987 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    Knight, Goodwin Jess - 1957
    Knopf, Alfred A. - 1951
    Knorr, Klaus - 1958
    Knowland, William F. - 1957
    Knox, Judge - 1964
    Koch, Edward I. - 1969-1987 (3 letters in the same folder)
    Kohn, Hans - 1959-1962 (3 letters)
    Kollek, Theodore - 1952-1959 (2 letters)
    Kolodin, Irving - 1961
    Koussevitzky, Olga (Mrs. Serge) - 1959-1962 (3 letters)
    Koussevitzky, Serge - 1950
    Kramer, Hilton - 1959
    Krim, Arthur B. - 1967
    Kuchel, Thomas Henry - 1957-1967 (4 letters)
  - Lam-Lan - Individuals, 1957-1967 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    Lama, Dalai - 1960
    Landon, Alfred Mossman - 1957
    Landrum, Philip Mitchell - 1966
    Lang, Pearl - 1964-1967 (8 letters)
    Lange, Dorothea - 1964-1965 (5 letters)
    Langer, Lawrence - 1958
  - Lar - Individuals, 1954-1967 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    Larkin, Oliver Waterman - 1957 (2 letters)
    Larsen, Roy Edward - 1954-1963 (9 letters)
  - Las-Lei - Individuals, 1953-1966 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Leo-Les - Individuals, 1958-1967 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    Leontief, Wassily - 1959-1967 (10 letters) Lerner, Max - 1962-1966 (3 letters)
    Lerner, Alan Jay - 1958
    Leslie, Alfred - 1959
  - Lev-Lil - Individuals, 1952-1967 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    Levi, Edward Hirsch - 1961-1967 (5 letters)
    Levi-Strauss, Claude - 1952-1959 (9 letters)
    Lilienthal, David E. - 1952
  - Lindsay - Individual, 1959-1967 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    Lindsay, John Vliet - 1959-1967 (14 letters)
  - Lodge - Individual, 1960-1966 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    Lodge, Henry Cabot - 1960-1966 (23 letters)
  - Lodge-Low, 1956-1969 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    Lodge, John Davis - 1956
    Logue, Edward Joseph - 1965-1966 (4 letters)
    Lopez, Lino M. - 1962
    Long, Russell Billiu - 1966
    Loudon, Jonkheer John Hugo - 1966
    Low, Robert A. - 1959
    Lowry, Bates - 1969
  - Mac-May - Individuals (3 folders), 1952-1967 (Box 8, Folder 70-72)
    McBride, Robert H. - 1966
    McCann, Kevin - 1957
    McCarthy, Eugene Joseph - 1961
    McClelland, David C. - 1955
    McCloy, John Jay - 1964
    McCormack, John W. - 1958 (2 letters)
    McCracken, Paul Winston - 1958
    McCrea, William S. - 1964
    McDowell, Harris B., Jr. - 1963
    McGee, Gale W. - 1961
    McGhee, George Crews - 1951-1964 (2 letters)
    McGovern, George - 1961-1967 (12 letters)
    McGraw, Donald Cushing - 1956
    McKissick, Floyd Bixler - 1966
    McKeldin, Theodore R. - 1957 (2 letters)
    MacLeish, Archibald - 1962
    McLuhan, Marshall - 1954-1964 (6 letters)
    McVicker, Roy H. - 1966
    Maddox, Lester - 1967
    Magnuson, Warren Grant - 1959
    Maheu, Rene - 1966
    Mann, Theodore D. - 1966-1967 (3 letters)
    Mansfield, Mike - 1959-1967 (4 letters)
    Marcus, Stanley - 1959-1963 (2 letters)
    Marin, Luis Munoz - 1958
    Marshall, George C. - 1952 (2 letters)
    Mason, Edward Sagendorph - 1961
    Masters, William Howell - 1960 (2 letters)
    Mays, Benjamin Elijah - 1964-1967 (21 folders)
  - Me-Mi - Individuals (2 folders), 1952-1967 (Box 9, Folder 73-74)
    Mead, Margaret - 1952-1961 (12 letters)
    Meany, George - 1966
    Melchior, Lauritz - 1965
    Menninger, William Claire - 1956
    Menuhin, Yehudi - 1958-1963 (6 letters)
    Merton, Robert K. - 1954-1960 (4 letters)
    Metcalf, Lee - 1963
    Mettger, H. Philip - 1959
    Miller, Arthur - 1967
    Mills, Wilbur Daigh - 1966
    Minow, Newton Norman - 1957
    Mintoff, Dom. - 1958
    Miura, Hideo - 1960
  - Mo-Mu - Individuals (3 folders), 1951-1988 (Box 9, Folder 75-77)
    Mondale, Walter Frederick – 1966-1988 (4 letters)
    Monnet, Jean - 1962 (2 letters)
    Montoya, Joseph M. - 1967 (2 letters)
    Monroney, Aimer Stillwell Mike - 1961
    Moore, George Stevens - 1964
    Moore, Paul, Jr. - 1963
    Morgan, Frederick - 1958-1967 (4 letters)
    Morgenthau, Hans Joachim - 1952-1961 (12 letters)
    Morgenthau, Henry, III - 1961-1963 (2 letters)
    Morgenthau, Robert Morris - 1965
    Morse, Wayne - 1955-1960 (3 letters)
    Moses, Robert - 1956-1962 (10 letters)
    Motherwell, Robert - 1958-1961 (3 letters)
    Moulder, Morgan M. - 1959
    Moynihan, Daniel Patrick - 1964-1968 (8 letters)
    Mumford, L. Quincy - 1963-1969 (3 letters - one letter was found in a folder with two nomination forms from John Houseman that the Ford Foundation received in 1963)
    Mundt, Karl Earl - 1955-1960 (3 letters)
    Murphy, George - 1958
    Murphy, Michael J. - 1965
    Murray, James Edward - 1951
    Murrow, Edward R. - 1961-1963 (6 letters)
    Muskie, Edmund Sixtus - 1956-1987 (6 letters)
  - N - Individuals (2 folders), 1951-1969 (Box 9, Folder 78-79)
    Nehru, Jawaharlal - 1952
    Nelson, Gaylord - 1966-1969 (2 letters)
    Neuberger, Richard Lewis - 1956
    Neustadt, Richard Elliott - 1961-1967 (5 letters)
    Newsom, Carroll Vincent - 1967
    Niebuhr, Reinhold - 1951 (6 letters)
    Nixon, Richard - 1954-1965 (3 letters)
    Norstad, Lauris - 1964
    Nyquist, Ewald B. - 1963-1964 (3 letters)
  - O - Individuals, 1951-1964 (Box 10, Folder 80)
    O'Connor, Frank D. - 1963
    O'Hara, Geoffrey - 1959
    O'Hara, Gerald P. - 1951
    Oppenheimer, Robert - 1951-1959 (9 letters)
    Ormandy, Eugene - 1964 (2 letters)
  - Pa-Pe - Individuals (3 folders), 1956-1968 (Box 10, Folder 81-83)
    Papandreou, Andreas G. - 1960-1964 (10 letters)
    Papp, Joseph - 1958-1964 (5 letters)
    Patman, Wright - 1961-1964 (26 letters)
    Patterson, Richard C. Jr. - 1962
    Paulus P P. VI (Pope Paul VI) - 1965
    Peabody, Endicott - 1964
    Pearson, Lester Bowles - 1960-1962 (9 letters)
    Peck, Gregory - 1958-1962 (2 letters)
    Pell, Claiborne 1961-1966 (3 letters)
    Percy, Charles Harting - 1956-1968 (8 letters)
    Persons, Wilton B. - 1959
    Peterson, Avery F. - 1959
  - Pi-Pu - Individuals (2 folders), 1954-1967 (Box 10, Folder 84-85)
    Piaget, Jean - 1954-1964 (17 letters)
    Pike, James Albert - 1957
    Plimpton, George - 1963
    Poitier, Sidney - 1967
    Porter, Charles O. - 1958-1960 (2 letters)
    Pozzatti, Rudy - 1959 (2 letters)
    Proxmire, William - 1965 (2 letters)
    Puharich, Henry K. - 1959
    Pulitzer, Joseph, Jr. - 1960
    Pusey, Merlo John - 1958 (5 letters)
    Pusey, Nathan M. - 1964-1966 (2 letters)
    Pusey, William Webb, III - 1961
  - Q - Individuals, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 86)
    Quie, Albert Harold - 1959
  - Ra-Ri - Individuals (2 folders), 1956-1967 (Box 11, Folder 87-88)
    Rabb, Ellis - 1962
    Radhakrishnan, Shri Nehru - 1964
    Randolph, A. Philip - 1965
    Randolph, Jennings - 1963
    Ray, Diry Lee - 1961
    Reed, Henry Hope - 1967
    Reed, John Hathaway - 1965
    Reischauer, Edwin O. - 1957-1965 (6 letters)
    Reuss, Henry Schoellkopf - 1959
    Reuther, Walter Philip - 1959-1962 (3 letters)
    Rhodes, James A. - 1956
    Ribicoff, Abraham - 1961
    Richardson, Elliot Lee - 1961-1967 (7 letters)
    Riesman, David - 1957
    Ripley, Sidney Dillon - 1964 (2 letters)
    Rivers, L. Mendel - 1956
  - Ro-Ry - Individuals (4 folders), 1950-1969 (Box 11, Folder 89-92)
    Rockefeller, David - 1960-1962 (4 letters)
    Rockefeller, Jeannette (Mrs. Winthrop) - 1961
    Rockefeller, John D., III - 1950-1967 (15 letters)
    Rockefeller, Laurance S. - 1961-1966 (4 letters)
    Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich - 1951-1968 (18 letters)
    Rodino, Peter Wallace, Jr. - 1959
    Rogers, Carl Ransom - 1955-1957 (8 letters)
    Rogers, Paul Grant - 1959
    Romney, George - 1960-1965 (2 letters)
    Ronan, William John - 1960 (2 letters)
    Roosevelt, Eleanor (Mrs. Franklin D.) - 1956 (2 letters)
    Roosevelt, James - 1964
    Roper, Elmo - 1959
    Rorem, Ned - 1961
    Rosellini, Albert D. - 1964
    Rostow, Eugene Victor - 1956-1966 (4 letters)
    Rostow, Walt Whitman - 1959-1969 (3 letters)
    Roszak, Theodore - 1958-1967 (9 letters)
    Rothschild, Lord Victor - 1958
    Rudel, Julius - 1966-1967 (2 letters)
    Rudolph, Paul - 1962
    Rumsfeld, Donald - 1966
    Rusk, Dean - 1956-1967 (17 letters)
    Russell, Richard Brevard - 1963
    Ryan, William Fitts - 1961-1966 (3 letters)
  - Sa-Sc - Individuals (2 folders), 1951-1967 (Box 12, Folder 93-94)
    Salinger, Pierre - 1966
    Salk, Jonas - 1966
    Samuelson, Paul Anthony - 1957-1961 (4 letters)
    Sanford, Terry - 1961-1967 (16 letters)
    Sargeant, Winthrop - 1967
    Scheuer, James H. - 1965
    Schlesinger, Arthur, Jr. - 1955-1963 (11 letters)
    Schlesinger, Arthur Meier - 1955-1958 (2 letters)
    Schneider, Alan - 1958
    Schumann, Robert - 1954
    Schweitzer, Albert - 1951-1954 (5 letters)
    Schwengel, Fred - 1959
    Scott, Hugh - 1959-1967 (2 letters)
    Scranton, William Warren - 1967
  - Sh-So - Individuals (3 folders), 1954-1967 (Box 12, Folder 95-97)
    Shafer, Raymond Philip - 1967 (2 letters)
    Shahn, Ben - 1958-1959 (2 letters)
    Shapp, Milton J. - 1962-1964 (2 letters)
    Shaw, Irwin - 1958
    Shawn, Ted - 1961-1964 (5 letters)
    Shriver, Eunice Kennedy (Mrs. Robert Sargent, Jr.) - 1961-1966 (4 letters)
    Shriver, Robert Sargent, Jr. - 1961-1965 (8 letters)
    Shuster, George - 1960
    Siscoe, Frank G. - 1961-1965 (7 letters)
    Sisk, Bernice Frederic - 1957
    Skinner, Burrhus Frederic - 1956-1963 (17 letters)
    Skouras, Spyros P. - 1954 (2 letters)
    Smathers, George -1958 (2 letters)
    Smith, David - 1959-1961 (2 letters)
    Smith, Hulett Carlson - 1965 (3 letters)
    Snow, Charles P. - 1962
    Sokoloff, Boris - 1962
    Sorel, Claudette - 1958 (2 letters)
  - Sp-Sz - Individuals (2 folders), 1950-1967 (Box 12, Folder 98-99)
    Spellman, Francis Cardinal - 1954-1957 (4 letters)
    Spivak, Lawrence Edmund - 1959-1962 (2 letters)
    Stans, Maurice Hubert - 1959
    Stanton, Frank - 1956-1957 (4 letters)
    Stassen, Harold Edward - 1950-1954 (5 letters)
    Stern, Fritz - 1965
    Stevenson, Adlai Ewing - 1957-1964 (7 letters)
    Stimpson, Harry F., Jr. - 1959
    Stokowski, Leopold - 1957-1963 (5 letters)
    Strasberg, Lee - 1963
    Stratton, Julius Adams - 1956-1967 (4 letters)
    Strauss, Lewis L. - 1952
    Sulzberger, Arthur Ochs - 1966 (2 letters)
    Surrey, Stanley Sterling - 1963-1965 (2 letters)
    Symington, James Wadsworth - 1966 (2 letters)
    Szell, George - 1967 (5 letters)
    Szillard, Leo - 1962
  - T - Individuals (2 folders), 1956-1967 (Box 13, Folder 100-101)
    Taft, William Howard III - 1957
    Talbot, Phillips - 1962
    Talmadge, Herman Eugene - 1959
    Tate, James Hugh Joseph - 1964
    Taylor, Maxwell Davenport - 1956-1957 (2 letters)
    Thebom, Blanche - 1958-1962 (4 letters)
    Thiebaud, Wayne - 1959
    Thomas, Lowell - 1962
    Thompson, Frank, Jr. - 1962-1966 (2 letters)
    Thompson, Llewellyn E. - 1961-1962 (2 letters)
    Thomson, Keith - 1959
    Thomson, Virgil - 1961 (2 letters)
    Thomson, Vernon Wallace - 1957
    Thurmond, Strom - 1957
    Trilling, Lionel - 1963-1965 (4 letters)
    Tudor, Antony - 1961
    Tunney, John Varick - 1967
    Tworkov, Jack - 1959
    Tydings, Joseph Davies - 1966 (4 letters)
  - U - Individuals, 1956-1967 (Box 13, Folder 102)
    Udall, Stewart L. - 1956
    Ullman, Al - 1959
    Unruh, Jesse Marvin - 1964-1967 (4 letters)
    U Thant - 1961-1963 (5 letters)
    Ustinov, Peter - 1967
  - V - Individuals, 1951-1969 (Box 13, Folder 103)
    Valenti, Jack Joseph - 1969
    Van Ky, Tran - 1961
    Vandenberg, Arthur Hendrick, Jr. - 1951
    Volpe, John Anthony - 1966
  - Wa-We - Individuals, 1954-1966 (Box 13, Folder 104)
    Wagner, Friedelind - 1959-1964 (2 letters)
    Wagner, Richard - 1962
    Wagner, Robert F. - 1958-1966 (8 letters)
    Wallace, Mike - 1957
    Wallach, Eli - 1959
    Wallenstein, Alfred - 1959
    Wanamaker, John Rodman - 1964
    Warfield, William - 1958
    Warren, Earl - 1954-1957 (3 letters)
    Watson, Thomas J., Jr. - 1959
    Weese, Harry - 1964
    Weicker, Mrs. Lowell - 1965
    Westmoreland, William Childs - 1962
  - Wh-Wz - Individuals (2 folders), 1951-1969 (Box 13, Folder 105-106)
    White, Leonard D. - 1957
    White, Paul Dudley - 1956
    White, Poppy Cannon - 1962
    White, Theodore Harold - 1964
    White, Walter - 1951
    Whitney, John Hay - 1961-1967 (2 letters)
    Wiggins, James Russell - 1957
    Wilkins, Roy - 1963-1969 (4 letters)
    Wilkinson, C. Bud - 1962
    Williams, Harrison Arlington, Jr. - 1963-1965 (5 letters)
    Wilson, Harold - 1958-1968 (4 letters)
    Wirtz, W. Willard - 1962-1966 (3 letters)
    Woods, Rose Mary - 1955
    Wyzanski, Charles Edward, Jr. - 1954-1966 (19 letters)
  - Y - Individuals, 1951-1975 (Box 13, Folder 107)
    Yamasaki, Minoru - 1961-1962 (2 letters)
    Yarborough, Ralph - 1959
    Yarmolinsky, Adam - 1965
    Yorty, Samuel William - 1951-1969 (2 letters)
    Young, Andrew J. - 1967-1975 (8 letters)
    Young, Philip - 1959 (2 letters)
    Young, Whitney Moore Jr. - 1961-1970 (16 letters)
  - Z - Individuals, 1957-1961 (Box 13, Folder 108)
    Zellerbach, James David - 1957-1958 (3 letters)
    Zorach, William - 1961
  - Questionable and miscellaneous correspondence, 1951-1965 (Box 14, Folder 109)
    Benton, William - 1951
    Origo, Iris - 1962
    Hagen, Uta - 1964
    Griffin, William V. - 1955
    Burdick, Quentin N. - 1964
    Byrd, Harry F. - 1958
    Dmitri, Ivan - 1962 (3 letters)
    Hughes, Richard J. - 1964
    Fullbright, J.W. - 1960-1961 (3 letters)
    O. Douglass, William - 1962
    Case, Clifford P. - 1964
    Hatfield, Mark O. - 1963
    Eisenhower, Milton S. - 1963
    Hesburgh, Theodore M. - 1963
    Cole, Charles W. - 1963
    Clark, Grenville - 1963
    Prince Bernhard of the Netherlands - 1965
    Adrian, Edgar Douglass - 1957
    Eisenhower, Dwight David - 1953
    Kohn, Hans - undated
    Hoff, Phillip H. - 1965
    Hunter, Kermit - 1958-1960 (2 letters from individual and 2 letters to individual)
    Wells, Herman B. and Hesburgh, Theordore M. - 1959
    Hoff, Phillip H. - 1963
    Hardwicke, Cedric - 1953
    Harriman, W. Averell - 1959
    Keating, Kenneth B. - 1961
    King Paul of Greece - 1959
    Baskin, Leonard - 1952
    Ben-Haim, Paul - 1958
    Kazan, Molly - undated
    Unidentified individual - 1960
    The Duke of Norfolk - 1960
    Unidentified individual - 1963
    It appears that the correspondence in this file is marked questionable because the Ford Foundation Archives was attempting to identify and verify some of the letters' signatures.
  - Loose correspondence: Adolphus - Kazan (2 folders), 1953-1974 (Box 14, Folder 110-111)
    Adolphus, Gustavus (King of Sweden) - 1966
    Bass, Perkins - 1957
    Byrd, Harry F. - 1974
    Udall, Stewart Lee - 1967
    Bunche, Ralph J. - 1960-1968 (2 letters)
    Brzezinski, Zbigniew (Zbig) - 1968
    Ford, Henry II - 1968
    Magloire, Paul - 1954
    Cohelan, Jeffery - 1967
    Caen, Herb - circa 1965-1968
    Eisenhower, Dwight - 1953
    Fairbank, John K. - 1961-1969 (5 letters)
    Freeman, Orville - 1967
    Frankel, Charles - 1966 (3 letters)
    Fubini, Eugene G. - 1967
    Fulbright, James William - 1966-1969 (2 letters)
    Gardner, John W. - 1965
    Gilmore, Voit - 1967 (2 letters)
    Godwin, Mills E. Jr. - 1974
    Goheen, Robert F. - 1966 (2 letters)
    Goldberg, Arthur J. - 1966
    Graf, Herbert - 1967
    Grider, George W. - 1966
    Gruening, Ernest - undated
    Catlin, George E. G. - 1967
    Gallagher, Cornelius E. - 1966
    Grabowski, Bernard F. - 1966
    Graham, Martha - 1966
    Hammer, Armand - 1967
    Hampton, Lionel - 1968
    Hancock, Herbie - 1969
    Hanks, Nancy (Secretary for Laurance S. Rockefeller) - 1968 (2 letters)
    Hanna, Richard T. - 1966-1967 (4 letters)
    Hatfield, Mark O. - 1969 (3 letters)
    Healey, Dennis - 1967 (4 letters)
    Heath, Edward - 1969
    Heckscher, August - 1966
    Heiskell, Andrew - 1966
    Herter, Christian A. - 1966
    Hesburgh, Theodore Martin - 1966 (2 letters)
    Park Chung Hee - 1967
    Hitchcock, Alfred - 1963
    Horton, Frank - 1966
    Humphrey, Hubert H. - 1965-1973 (7 letters)
    Harris, Fred - 1966-1969 (5 letters)
    Hartke, Vance - 1969
    Hoff, Philip H. - 1967
    Javits, Jacob K. - 1967-1973 (8 letters)
    Johnson, Harold T. (Bizz) - 1967
    Tydings, Joseph D. - 1969
    Katz, Milton - 1963-1966 (6 letters)
    Kazan, Elia - 1963
    There is not a consistent alphabetical organization for the signature letters from individuals found within this file. Letters were not rearranged during processing in order to create an alphabetical organization.
  - Loose correspondence: Kennedy - Kissinger, 1962-1967 (Box 14, Folder 112)
    Kennedy, John F. - 1962
    Kennedy, Robert F. - 1967
    Keppel, Francis - 1967
    Kirk, Grayson - 1966
    Kissinger, Henry A. - 1965-1967 (2 letters)
  - Loose correspondence: Kuchel - Lindsay, 1960-1969 (Box 14, Folder 113)
    Kuchel, Thomas H. - 1967
    Multiple individuals (petitions for the National Repertory Theatre) - 1964
    Firestone, Harvey S. Jr. - 1962
    Hoover, John Edgar - 1960
    Larsen, Roy E. - 1966
    Lasker, Mary (Mrs. Albert D. Lasker) - 1966
    Leontief, Wassily - 1966-1969 (4 letters)
    Lindsay, John V. - 1966-1968 (2 letters)
- Mills Committee, 1969; 3
  In the lead up to the passing of the 1969 Tax Act, the House Ways and Means Committee, chaired by Representative Wilbur Mills, requested that Ford Foundation President McGeorge Bundy appear before the committee. He was asked to explain what some saw as political bias in recent Ford Foundation grants. Among the controversial programs were grants to the Cleveland Congress of Racial Equality (CORE) and the Southern Regional Council for voter registration activities, the travel and study awards to Robert Kennedy's staff following his assassination, and support for the Yale Law School's League for Environmental Law.
  This series contains correspondence, press releases, and summaries related to 12 of the 19 controversial grants. Materials were originally in a binder but were removed and placed into folders for preservation purposes. The original order was retained.
  - Mills Committee - Volume 2 (3 folders), 1969 (Box 2, Folder 27-29)
    Sections include:
    1. Southwest Council of La Raza
    2. The North Carolina Fund
    3. Southern Christian Leadership Foundation
    4. School Decentralization
    5. Kennedy Travel and Study Awards
    6. Voter Registration/Education (Including Cleveland CORE)
    7. Urban Affairs Foundation
    8. Urban Training Center for Christian Missions
    9. Lawyers' Committee for Civil Rights
    10. League for Environmental Law (Yale Law School)
    11. Allied Builders Union
    12. United States National Student Association Grant
- Oversize Materials, 1982-1986; 4
  Oversize materials signed by Ronald Reagan
  - National Philanthropy Day 1986 Proclamation signed by Ronald Reagan (Box 15, Folder 114)
  - Award for National Excellence, U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development - Certificate signed by Ronald Reagan, 1982 November (Box 15, Folder 115)
    Awarded to South Bronx 2000 - Local Development Corporation